Hold your breath.
Pressure is a drama, thriller film directed by Ron Scalpello.
Four divers are stuck deep underwater in a vessel
after a freak storm destroys their ship.
Will they survive?
Engel, played by Danny Huston.
Mitchell, played by Matthew Goode.
Jones, played by Joe Cole.
Hurst, played by Alan McKenna.
Karsen, played by Ian Pirie.
Emily Lou, played by Daisy Lowe.
Pressure is a 2015 British disaster survival film directed by Ron Scalpello.
It tells the story of four men who get stuck at the
bottom of the ocean in a diving bell.
The film explores themes of survival, scuba diving, underwater.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.